THEY SAID IT THEMSELVES [Sources: city minutes, resolutions & ballot — on file]
JAN 12, 2026 — Few resources [Res. #6507, Consolidated Plan 2025–2027 · Jan 12, 2026]
48 HOURS LATER — $22,000,000 [Committee of the Whole minutes · Jan 14, 2026]
THE BALLOT, itemized — $0 for treatment [Sixth-penny ballot propositions · Aug 18, 2026 primary]
THEIR OWN WORDS — Lipstick on a pig [Vicki Nemecek, Public Works Director · COTW Jan 14, 2026]
MEANWHILE, THE NUMBERS — 214 people [Published WTE arrest blotter, Dec 2016–Feb 2026 (19,795 bookings)]
APR 13, 2026 — ONE NIGHT [City Council agenda & minutes · Apr 13, 2026]
APR 27, 2026 — ON CONSENT [Council minutes · Apr 27, 2026 (35+ speakers)]
THE FINDING — Future occupants [Annexation ordinance vs. staff report · spring 2026]
5.26% — A NECK [PUDC-26-38 staff report & packet metrics · Apr 2026]
MAR 9, 2026 — 5–5. TWICE. [Council minutes · Mar 9, 2026 (47 speakers, past 11 p.m.)]
THIS ISN’T A CONSPIRACY — IT’S THE RECORD [cheyenne.granicus.com · cheyennecity.org · Laramie County election results]